Carlton Foust Papers, 1959-2003 and undated foustcarlton
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Audiovisual Materials, (1 box)
  - JWT Chicago--Kellogg's Sales Meeting, Leadership as an Attitude. USMC compliation: Power, Warriors, Most Powerful Weapon, Globe, Chess, Knight, Always. 1995. Umatic NTSC. TRT: 4:00.
  - JWT London--Lux compilation reel. 1995. Umatic NTSC. TRT: 30:00.
  - Skytel: Señales, Encima, Mensajes. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00.
  - TBWA--St. Louis Blues. 1983. Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00.